var questionSet = [
    {
        question: "What does HTML stand for?",
        answers: ["A) Hyper Text Markup Language","B) Hydro Temp Market Legend","C) Hyphen Text Markup Lesson","D) Hyper Touch Module Learning"],
        correct: "A"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 2",
        answers: ["A) Lorem slipsum","B) Jimmy Neutron Sausage","C) Mario Andretti Robot","D) Doctor What"],
        correct: "B"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 3",
        answers: ["A) Lorem slipsum","B) Jimmy Neutron Sausage","C) Mario Andretti Robot","D) Doctor What"],
        correct: "B"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 4",
        answers: ["A) Lorem slipsum","B) Jimmy Neutron Sausage","C) Mario Andretti Robot","D) Doctor What"],
        correct: "B"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 5",
        answers: ["A) Lorem slipsum","B) Jimmy Neutron Sausage","C) Mario Andretti Robot","D) Doctor What"],
        correct: "B"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 6",
        answers: ["A) Lorem slipsum","B) Jimmy Neutron Sausage","C) Mario Andretti Robot","D) Doctor What"],
        correct: "B"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 7",
        answers: ["A) Lorem slipsum","B) Jimmy Neutron Sausage","C) Mario Andretti Robot","D) Doctor What"],
        correct: "B"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 8",
        answers: ["A) Lorem slipsum","B) Jimmy Neutron Sausage","C) Mario Andretti Robot","D) Doctor What"],
        correct: "B"
    },

    {
        question: "Question 9",
        answers: ["A) Lorem slipsum","B) Jimmy Neutron Sausage","C) Mario Andretti Robot","D) Doctor What"],
        correct: "B"
    },
    
    {
        question: "Question 10",
        answers: ["A) Lorem slipsum","B) Jimmy Neutron Sausage","C) Mario Andretti Robot","D) Doctor What"],
        correct: "B"
    }
]